const STORE = [{
        question: "what year did Chelsea win the champions League final?",
        choices: ["2012", "2011", "2013", "2014"],
        answer: "2012",
    },
    {
        question: "what color was the jersey for the UCL final",
        choices: ["blue", "red", "black", "white"],
        answer: 'blue',

    },
    {
        question: "Who scored the final penalty",
        choices: ["Juan Mata", "Drogba", "Fernando Torres", "David Luiz"],
        answer: 'Drogba',
    },
    {
        question: "Which team did Chelsea play in the champions league final?",
        choices: ["Bayern Munich", "Barcelona", "Inter Milan", "Ac Milan"],
        answer: 'Bayern Munich',

    },

    {
        question: "Who was the goalkeeper for that game?",
        choices: ["Edwin Van Der start", "julio Cesar", "dida", "Peter Cech"],
        answer: 'Peter Cech',
    },

    {
        question: "Who did Chelsea defeat to get to the final",
        choices: ["Inter Milan", "Barcelona", "Arsenal", "AC Milan"],
        answer: "Barcelona",

    },

    {
        question: " Who was the coach during the ucl final",
        choices: ["Roberto Di Matteo", "Luis Felipe Scolari", "Carlos Ancelotti", "Jose Mourinho"],
        answer: 'Roberto Di Mateo'
    },
    {
        question: "Which player did not start the match",
        choices: ["Juan Mata", "Ramires", "John Obi Mikel", "David Luiz"],
        answer: "Ramires",
    },
    {
        question: "How did Chelsea score to go into penalties",
        choices: ["Off a corner kick", "strike outside of the 18 yard box", "Bicycle kick", "Dribble through Jerome Boateng"],
        answer: "Off a corner Kick"
    },
    {
        question: "How many finals did Chelsea win before",
        choices: ["3", "0", "4", "5"],
        answer: "0"
    }
];